=Betrayed Love=
= الحب المغدور =
=Episode 11=
= الحلقة 11 =
I'll go make breakfast first.
سأذهب لإعداد الفطور أولاً.
Enjoy your breakfast.
استمتع بوجبة الإفطار.
It's been so many days.
لقد مرت أيام عديدة.
It's time to forget it.
حان الوقت لنسيانها.
Not everything can be forgotten even if that's what you want.
لا يمكن نسيان كل شيء حتى لو كان هذا ما تريده.
I will let you see me change.
سأدعك تراني أتغير.
(I really want to forget it.)
(أريد حقًا أن أنساه.)
(But I don't know if any secrets that I can't find out)
(لكنني لا أعرف ما إذا كان هناك أي أسرار لا أستطيع اكتشافها)
(are hidden beneath Shen Zhuo's seemingly gentle smile.)
(مخبأة تحت ابتسامة Shen Zhuo اللطيفة على ما يبدو).
(Can our life get on the right track from now on?)
(هل يمكن أن تسير حياتنا على المسار الصحيح من الآن فصاعدًا؟)
It's said that the audit has been completed,
يقال أن التدقيق قد اكتمل ،
and the money has been returned to the company.
وتمت إعادة الأموال إلى الشركة.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Xin, he didn't hurt you again, did he?
شين ، لم يؤذيك مرة أخرى ، أليس كذلك؟
Everything is all right with me.
كل شيء على ما يرام معي.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I can continue to help you
يمكنني الاستمرار في مساعدتك
if you need me to do it.
إذا كنت تريد مني أن أفعل ذلك.
You've helped me a lot.
لقد ساعدتني كثيرا.
I no longer want to get you involved.
لم أعد أريد أن أشركك.
I did those things for you willingly.
لقد فعلت هذه الأشياء من أجلك عن طيب خاطر.
Yang Zhe, don't worry.
يانغ زهي ، لا تقلق.
I'm really doing well.
أنا بخير حقًا.
That's good. You must protect yourself well from now on.
هذا جيد.  يجب أن تحمي نفسك جيدًا من الآن فصاعدًا.
Yang Zhe! Hello?
يانغ زهي!  مرحبًا؟
Yang Zhe, can you hear me?
يانغ زهي ، هل تسمعني؟
What? Miss Guan plagiarized?
ماذا؟  ملكة جمال جوان مسروقة؟
No way!
مستحيل!
Exactly.
بالضبط.
This is a student's work published on the network platform.
هذا عمل طالب منشور على منصة الشبكة.
Now it is trending on social media.
الآن هو يتجه على وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي.
This design draft has been used to produce ready-to-wear clothes.
تم استخدام مسودة التصميم هذه لإنتاج ملابس جاهزة.
But now, from style elements to color scheme,
ولكن الآن ، من عناصر النمط إلى نظام الألوان ،
it resembles the graduation work of that college student.
إنه يشبه عمل التخرج لطالب الكلية.
As a result, the factory had to stop production.
نتيجة لذلك ، اضطر المصنع إلى إيقاف الإنتاج.
Mr. Wang, let's not talk about the production.
سيد وانغ ، دعونا لا نتحدث عن الإنتاج.
What about our company's reputation now?
ماذا عن سمعة شركتنا الآن؟
I have just received three or four letters from lawyers,
لقد تلقيت للتو ثلاث أو أربع رسائل من المحامين ،
all of which are about compensation and termination of contracts.
كل ذلك يتعلق بالتعويضات وإنهاء العقود.
I've asked my assistant to investigate it.
لقد طلبت من مساعدي التحقيق في الأمر.
But now we can't find that college student.
لكن الآن لا يمكننا العثور على ذلك الطالب الجامعي.
This problem occurred during my tenure,
حدثت هذه المشكلة خلال فترة ولايتي ،
so I will take full responsibility.
لذلك سوف أتحمل المسؤولية كاملة.
Isn't this Miss Guan?
أليست هذه ملكة جمال جوان؟
Yes.
نعم.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I'll handle it. I'll escort you back first.
أنا التعامل معها.  سأرافقك للعودة أولاً.
I can do it myself.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Miss Guan.
ملكة جمال جوان.
Shen Zhuo!
شين تشو!
She is romantically involved with another man.
إنها متورطة عاطفيًا مع رجل آخر.
You still can't come back to me?
مازلت لا تستطيع العودة إلي؟
Xu Jing, to my surprise,
شو جينغ ، لدهشتي ،
it turned out you did all these things.
اتضح أنك فعلت كل هذه الأشياء.
A woman who is driven mad
امرأة مدفوعة بالجنون
stops at nothing.
يتوقف عند لا شيء.
No matter what Guan Xin did wrong,
بغض النظر عن الخطأ الذي ارتكبه Guan Xin ،
she and I are a family.
هي وأنا عائلة.
We've decided to resume our marital life.
لقد قررنا استئناف حياتنا الزوجية.
Don't come to see me again.
لا تأتي لرؤيتي مرة أخرى.
I don't want to see you again in all my life.
لا أريد أن أراك مرة أخرى في كل حياتي.
Now get out of my face immediately!
الآن اخرج من وجهي على الفور!
I won't give up easily!
لن أستسلم بسهولة!
(From style elements to color scheme,)
(من عناصر النمط إلى نظام الألوان ،)
it resembles the graduation work of that college student.
إنه يشبه عمل التخرج لطالب الكلية.
(I have just received three or four letters from lawyers,)
(لقد تلقيت للتو ثلاث أو أربع رسائل من المحامين ،)
all of which are about compensation and termination of contracts.
كل ذلك يتعلق بالتعويضات وإنهاء العقود.
(This problem occurred during my tenure,)
(حدثت هذه المشكلة أثناء فترة ولايتي ،)
so I will take full responsibility.
لذلك سوف أتحمل المسؤولية كاملة.
You go find the original draft
تذهب للعثور على المسودة الأصلية
and try to find out the account
وحاول معرفة الحساب
that first published the design draft on the social media website.
التي نشرت مسودة التصميم لأول مرة على موقع التواصل الاجتماعي.
Isn't this Miss Guan?
أليست هذه ملكة جمال جوان؟
Yes.
نعم.